damn bro you sure did set up the living
room really well I can already tell this
party is going to be really bitchin you
know it and check this out I even found
this cheesecake in the fridge
you mean uncle Chuck's cheesecake bro
you know he told us not to eat that ha
ha ha who cares what he doesn't know
won't hurt him we'll just blame it on
Sonya or some
Sonic Manic look over there it looks
like our friends Knuckles Mindy and
Baird will be just arrived how's it
going I hope we're not late
Knuckles my man how's it going it's
going good
damn you really went all out on this
party didn't you when are the hot
going to show up I'm so glad you
could make it to my party Bartleby with
you here this is going to be the best
party ever but of course it might be
she's holding a party then I have to
come what kind of boyfriend would I be
if I didn't Oh Bartleby you are so sweet
and sexy I'm blushing not as sweet and
sexy as your big club ass big boy ha ha
ha Sonic
Bartleby come on can't you two get a
room somewhere or something all right I
hope you noobs are ready to dance like
there's no tomorrow called I'm turning
on the two
[Music]